[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
If you walk away, don’t ever come back again, you brat!
You stop seeing that boy right now!
(Seeing their family fight because Bay and I are together,)
I can’t help but feel guilty, Pa.
Just staying by my side
(and being cute like this is enough.)
I already know the truth about our family stealing Chun’s dim sum recipe.
(None of us did anything wrong.)
(I didn’t take Chun’s recipe)
(and you don’t have to feel guilty.)
Bee!
INCOMING CALL
Hello, mom.
(Bay, are you with your dad? I don’t know where he went.)
Mom.
Did you find Dad?
I couldn’t find him.
-Urg, where is he? -You couldn’t find him, either?
Obviously. And he’s not picking up his phone.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE
I can’t eat anymore.
Woman Let’s pack it home then.
Italy, yay!
Let’s go.
Food waste.
What are you looking at, uncle?!
What’s up, son?!
I didn’t know I was your dad’s brother.
Watch your mouth, old man.
Scumbag! I’m not all talk.
You don’t wanna mess with me…
Son of a b*tch!
Sh*t! Why did you punch me?!
How about that, uncle?
How about this?!
Easy!
Hey!
Hey! Bay!
No!
Now hold on! Are you trying to murder him?!
Easy!
-Officer! Officer! Officer! -Officer! Officer!
-Let’s go! -There’s a fight over here!
Get lost!
-Bay! -Bay!
Are you alright?
Why did you pick a fight with those guys?
You’re lucky we got there in time!
Bay.
I think we all should get some rest, son.
We can’t solve anything until everyone’s calmed down.
You’re his Pa now?
His damn Pa?
Great. Take everything from me.
Can you stop being a jerk?
No one has the energy to fight with you anymore.
Why don’t you stop babbling and get out of my face?
You need to stop.
Everyone risked their lives to save you today.
Don’t you have any gratitude?
You’re acting crazy and trying to control everyone
because you want to justify yourself, right?
That you weren’t wrong when you chose to betray Chun back then.
Am I right?
I’m sorry, Chun.
I’m sorry, kids.
I knew everything.
But I never tried to make it right.
If you want any compensation,
we’ll take responsibility for it.
If you call it quits, I’ll do the same.
I don’t want to take anything from you.
I only want you to leave me and my son alone. That’s all.
Tell Chun you’re sorry.
And just let Bay and Boat be.
Or else…
our marriage is over.
Honey…
Do you have to go that far?
Damn it.
I’ll go live with Mom.
Me, too.
What are you guys talking about?
Do you hate your dad that much? Huh?
Boat.
Honey.
You’re luckier than me that you still have a chance.
I’m sorry, Chun
I’m sorry.
Bay,
I’m sorry, son.
I’m sorry, Boat
I’m sorry, honey.
I’m sorry.
I really am.
This looks worse than I thought.
Are you sure you’re okay?
I’m okay.
Don’t worry about me.
You should go to sleep.
I don’t think I can.
Fortunately,
the tryout is in the evening.
Come get some sleep.
I can’t wait to fall asleep and wake up tomorrow.
Why?
Tomorrow, you’ll get to be in the national team.
And you and I will finally get to be together.
I’ve been waiting for this for so long, Son.
You…
don’t think there’s a chance I won’t make it?
No.
I always know you can do it.
I knew since we were eight.
Good night.
Good night
-Can I sleep on your pillow? -Come on.
CLOSED FOR ONE DAY. GONE TO SUPPORT MY SON
BUSINESS CLOSED
What are you smiling about, Chun?
I’m just closing for renovations.
I’ll reopen with an even better shop.
Now that you’re fixing your shop, why don’t you fix your attitude as well?
Fine.
I’ll be back with a brand-new attitude.
I’ll come up with an idea for my new shop.
I guarantee my business will kick your business’s ass.
It’ll be so good you’ll have to close your place down.
Why don’t you change the recipe for your dim sum, too?
You’ve been selling the same damn thing for a century.
Ptui!
TENNIS NATIONAL TEAM TRYOUT COMPETITION
You’ll start playing after the first match is over.
It should be around 7 PM. Please warm up beforehand.
-Okay. -Yes.
Bay!
(Based on what you’ve told me and the ECG results,)
it may have been caused by a severe blow to the chest from a hard object,
which caused his heart rhythm to become irregular.
For now, I’ve given him medication intravenously.
If you’ll excuse me.
Thank you.
I don’t think I can do this, Coach.
Sun, take a deep breath.
How can I focus while playing?
The match is about to start.
You have to believe you can do it.
Sun.
If Bay found out he was the reason you missed your chance, it would destroy him.
Sun, can you keep fighting?
Can you please do this for Bay?
Come on, Sun.
Sun, let’s go.
You’ve got this, Sun.
Damn, why does it have to be today?
Sun needs to win 2 more sets to get into the national team.
The opponent has scored really well.
Will Sun be able to do this?
If he wants to play professionally,
he has to do it, even if he has to play through his tears.
Ready?
Are you okay?
I’m ready.
Let’s begin then.
Hey.
It’s okay, son.
Come back. Come back.
It’s alright. You’re still good.
It’s okay, son. It’s okay.
Sun, Bay is in good hands.
Don’t worry.
I want you to focus only on this match, okay?
I know it’s hard
but I believe you can do this.
Go, Sun.
Sun, you’ve got this. Come on.
(Sun.)
If our dads still try to keep us apart like this,
when you’re competing in the national tryout,
I won’t be able to be there for you.
It’s okay.
Really?
Really.
Damn.
It’s not important if I’m there or not?
Of course, it is.
But there will be times when you can’t be there to cheer me on, right?
Like when you’re studying abroad.
If I held this against you,
how could we go on as a couple?
But I want you to know I’ll be cheering for you,
thinking about how well you’re playing,
concerning if you’re ahead or behind.
Just like when we played together.
I know.
Ugh, I still want to be there to cheer for you.
How about this?
I’ll keep playing tennis for a long time.
Until the day you come back to cheer me on in person.
Okay?
Okay, I’ll hurry back so I can cheer you on.
While I’m not there, just know I’m trying my best to come back for you.
♪ It’s time that we fall in love ♪
♪ It’s finally time for you and me to be in love ♪
♪ This very second belongs to you alone ♪
♪ My heartbeat says it's yours to own ♪
Let’s go, Sun.
-Yay! -That’s it!
-Yes! -Woo!
Sun is back.
Good job, son. Let’s go.
-Yeah! -Yes!
-Nice job -Nice job
Nice job, Sun.
Good job.
-Go. -Let’s go.
Almost there, Sun.
Give it your best shot.
Focus, Sun, focus.
(While I’m not there, just know I’m trying my best to come back for you.)
Yay!
Yes!
Fantastic!
It’s Match point, son. Hang in there.
Just one more, Sun. One more.
Almost there.
Come on, Sun.
Yay!!
Yay!
Amazing!
Great job!
-Well done! -Amazing!
Sun!
Bay’s awake.
-What? Really? -Bay’s awake.
-(Yay!) -(Woo!)
Bay!
You really did it. Nice job.
You’re not hurt anymore?
Mmm, I’m okay now.
You sure?
Don’t do this to me again.
I don’t want to, either.
I feel so bad.
I didn’t get to watch you play.
Don’t worry about it.
You had to recover.
But I’ve seen you on the phone.
You did great.
-Promise? -I promise. I promise.
Congratulations to all students graduating today.
From now on, you get to follow the path you chose for yourselves.
But l’d like you to know
CALCULUS, MY TOFU I’m always here to support you.
I’m always here to support you.
I wish you all good luck.
Hey, I got into the Faculty of Fine Arts.
-Wait. Are you serious? -Yeah.
-Damn. I’m happy for you. -Thanks, buddy.
So cool.
And what about you going to Italy?
Why did you take me here?
Since we’ve gone public, we barely came here anymore.
I have something to tell you.
I got accepted by a school in Italy.
And what did your parents say?
I’ve talked to them
and they said yes.
They did?!
You’ll really get to study abroad?
And you’re really okay with that?
-If you’re not, I can go to a university here… -You have to go.
You have to.
You’re not sad at all?
You seem more excited than I am.
What’s there to be sad about?
You go do what you love over there.
And I’ll do what I love over here.
When the time comes, we’ll get to be together again.
That’s all.
And you’re not afraid we’re gonna break up?
We don’t have to.
Didn’t you say it yourself that even though we weren’t together,
you’d still be cheering me on from there.
A good love
should be pushing you forward
not holding you back.
And…I’ll be supporting you from here, too.
You are so adorable.
You should adore me then.
I adore you.
Who wouldn’t love you, my little tofu?
We should’ve started dating when we were eight
so we had more time together before I leave.
Are you crazy?
You’re so silly.
Woo!
-Let’s share. -What’d you wanna eat?
Want some?
-You want it? -Want some?
-Here comes the pizza. -No, I’m good.
-Here’s the pizza. -Thank you.
-Come on. -Here we go.
-Share it. -I’ll go first.
That table, take this.
Hey, Bay, can you speak Italian?
-Of course, bonjour. -Bonjour my ass.
You jerk. I’ll poke you with a fork. Watch it.
There’s only one slide left?
Yeah.
-Where’s mine? -You’ll be in Italy. You can eat pizza every day.
-What the hell? I wanna eat it. -Do you want mine?
Hey.
I’m okay. You eat it, babe.
What’s with the baby voice?
-“You eat it, babe”, he said. -What are you talking about?
-You’ve never sweet talked to me like that. -Why? You’re not my boyfriend.
Or do you want to be?
I’m just kidding.
I’ll take the left-over home.
What are you whispering about?
I brought you pizza.
I didn’t have to, Boat. We got plenty of food here.
Boat loves his pizza.
He has tried all the pizza around the country.
He wanted to eat some today so he ordered it. Right?
-You know me, Dad. -I sure do.
If your son loves pizza that much,
why don’t you open a pizza shop?
-You two, enjoy. I’ll be outside -Okay
Is this edible?
Wanna try some?
If it’s not good, I’ll let you kick me in the face.
Can I kick you first and then I’ll try it?
Look at you.
This is life changing.
You go girl.
Go, go, go.
Yay!
You’re making me blush.
Have the kids been drinking?
It’s just their personality.
They’ve had a whole box of soda.
I think they’re drunk on sugar.
Will I ever get to see you two again?
You’ll be studying abroad.
And you’ll be with the national team.
You’ll forget about me.
No way. How can I forget you?
-Really. -Really.
You’ll see. I’ll be the best club leader.
And I will be the next PREM’S GAME champion.
Because I was there during your era and I got to play with you.
Bro, that’s fierce.
Hey, I won’t allow that.
What the hell?
-If you want to hug someone, go hug Petong. -What?
Go hug Petong. Stop it.
What? No, stop it.
No.
I’ve always considered you a friend.
I know. My friend, Chun.
My bestie. My ride or die.
Wow. “My ride or die”, he said?
They’re in love.
Are you still sad seeing these kids graduate?
Well…I am a little.
But this year, I feel a bit better.
How?
It’s because…
you’re not leaving with them.
I mean…
You can keep me company so I won’t get lonely.
You’re all talk.
You’d better not leave me and go date someone.
Why?
Why can’t I date someone?
No reason.
I just won’t allow it.
Hey, wait.
You idiot.
-That’s crazy. -Oh, hell no. Hell no.
Hey, girl.
Wait, hold on.
You should bring one more luggage.
No, I won’t. I’ve got too much stuff already.
But there’s still room for you to get in.
Wanna come with me?
Funny.
Try sitting on it. That might work.
Damn.
-There. Close it. -Yes.
Finally.
Took you long enough. Shouldn’t have spent your time playing games.
Before I leave,
let’s review our deal one more time.
-Well…we’ll text each other every day. -Mmm.
If there’s a problem or misunderstanding,
we’ll talk it out right away.
That’s right.
What about Sundays?
Video calls.
I’ve put you on my schedule for the next three years.
Good boy.
What if someone hits on you?
If someone hits on me,
-I’ll feed them to the crocodile. -Good boy.
You should stop teaching me to be weird like you.
I can’t.
I don’t want you to be cute with other people.
I had to teach you to be a little weird, okay?
My tofu.
Oww.
Let’s go now.
Ready? One…two…three.
I know I’ll miss you so much.
I know I’ll miss you more.
♪ Ever since that day ♪
♪ When you and I happened to meet, it’s like a dream ♪
♪ ’Cause you’re the one ♪
♪ Who came along and made my heart skip a beat ♪
♪ It feels like I’ve finally found love ♪
1 YEAR LATER
That’s all. Drive safely.
-2 boxes of Hawaiian pizza. Thank you so much. -Yes.
Hey, Bee!
Don’t you know how to manage your shop?
SAMING PHON FAI Look.
Your customers are standing on the street.
What, Chun?
You’re jealous of me already?
Why would I be?
I got lots of customers, too.
Where?
I can only count like 10 people.
-Yeah? -Yeah.
Are you freaking blind?
See how long my line is?
I got online orders, too.
-What’s wrong? Why are you standing like that? -Pa, enough.
-Pa. -What?
Your customers are hangry.
-Damn. -For my customers’ sake.
You’re gonna lose your customers because you’re so cocky.
What? What does that even mean?
-I have a business to run. -Yeah, I have a business to run, too.
Please, come in. This way.
Sun!
Hey!
Bay!
Damn.
You beat me again.
What are you doing here?
Why didn’t you tell me you were coming?
I wanted to surprise you.
You’re going to give a speech.
How could I miss it?
-No way. -Why?
You came back just watch me give a speech?
Fine, I’ll tell you the truth.
My university is on break.
So I’ll stay here for a month.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Why didn’t you tell me first?
Do you miss me that much?
Of course I do.
I haven’t seen you for so long.
When we talked on the phone,
you always acted tough.
Seeing how much you miss me, I’m relieved.
My tofu.
Hey, Bay, you can’t pinch my cheek in public.
I’m a national athlete now.
What if someone sees me?
-See? -Mmm.
See this flag?
Fine. I’ll stop doing that.
Pinching my cheek like that… I’m embarrassed.
Hey!
Did you just kiss my cheek?
You’re shy?
A little bit.
And do you like it?
Yes.
Come on. Let’s go to school.
You’re shy, huh?
What?
Next, I’d like to invite one of our alumni to come up and give a speech.
Good morning, everyone. My name’s Sun.
I’m an alumnus of this school.
How are you feeling on the last day of your high school life?
Are you glad?
Or are you worried about something?
I’m so glad.
I’m excited.
I used to be so afraid of change and saying goodbye.
Until I learned that every ending is also a new beginning.
I thought being an athlete made me understand that.
Because finishing one game means you’re starting another.
But that wasn’t the reason.
I realized those things weren’t scary
when I received genuine love
from the people in my life.
(My son came up with the pizza dough recipe himself.)
(It was love)
APPLICATION FOR WITHDRAWAL FROM UNIVERSITY (that made me realize I didn’t have to be someone else to be loved.)
I’ve got a new pizza recipe for you to try.
YOU ARE CORDIALLY INVITED TO CELEBRATE OUR WEDDING
(Love that will never change even when we do.)
I like the tennis term ‘love-all’.
‘Love’ sounds a bit like the French word for zero.
It’s used when a new game begins.
Our lives are not so different from a tennis match.
BUSINESS CLOSED
(I’d like all of you to believe)
(that every ending always has a new beginning waiting for you.)
Hello, Sun. What are you doing?
Taking a break.
-Is it raining there? -(But genuine love)
-Yeah, it’s just started to drizzle. -(makes the journey to your new beginning less scary.)
And when your new match begins,
shout, “Love-all” and start to play.
HE WAS RAISED WELL, HIS PASSION SHINES BRIGHT, FACE CARD NEVER DECLINED, OMG, GREAT SPEECH!
Sun’s speech was inspiring.
I know, right?
It made me feel like
I want to tell my crush I like him and get it over with.
So I can have my new beginning, too.
You still have a crush on that guy?
Of course.
What can I do?
I see him every day. Plus, he takes such good care of me.
How could I get over him?
Who is he?
You’re not gonna tell me?
You really wanna know?
Then…come closer.
Closer.
I have something to tell you, too.
Hmm?
Come closer.
Boat!
We’re at school!
Why are you yelling?
We can’t be doing this at school.
Can’t we?
What if the kids saw us?
-Free country. -Free country?!
Uhm…
Can I borrow Sun to play tennis with us?
I’d like to play against a national player for once.
Right, bro. I’ve been training so hard for this day.
Let me go. I’ll go play with these kids.
But I’m not done with you.
I’ll play with them for a bit.
Why don’t you play double then?
I’ve brought you your rackets.
Surprise!
-Hey! -Hey!
-Ooh. -Wow!
My My My.
Not matching rackets.
Matching rackets.
You got these made for us.
Mmm.
Thank you.
It’s a heart shape.
-Ready? Ready? -Let’s go!
-Come on. -Let’s go.
Come with me.
You were far better than me today.
Guess I have to practice the shadowing technique again.
So I can keep up with you.
Okay.
I’ll coach you.
Should we start training now?
Hey!
We’re still in sync.
No need to practice.
Who said I’m practicing?
This is a real match.
♪ Ever since that day ♪ Hey, you caught me off guard!
♪ When you and I happened to meet, -What? Come on. -Stay right there.
it’s like a dream ♪
♪ ’Cause you’re the one ♪
♪ Who came along and made my heart skip a beat ♪
♪ It feels like I’ve finally found love ♪
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE